Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
He has nothing to do
with the death of Josefina.
I have discovered
that they're planning to
execute Juanito.
On the 7th of December.
Mother Olivia took the fall
for what happened.
And because of that,
she was sentenced to death.
I am an angel, Carmela.
My name is Faida.
Olivia.
What would your father feel...
if I send him
your severed head?
Mercedes...
Cut off that woman's head!
And send it to her father!
Juanito!
Just go!
Go straight to that path!
- No!
- There's a river there!
- The guard's camp is over there!
- I'm not leaving you here, Juanito!
- You must escape!
- I will never leave you!
- Go now, Carmela!
I know the truth!
You had Josefina killed
and you kidnapped Angelito!
How could you?!
Juanito...
I apologize for not
informing you earlier...
But Theresita and I are in love.
I'm not afraid
of you anymore, okay?
Whoever Juanito loves,
I love too.
And starting today,
if it's alright with you,
I'll be your mother.
I have been waiting for you,
but you were not in your room.
I already warned you
not to hurt my siblings again.
You're lying!
Miss.
Did Natasha see you wearing those?
So what?
Maybe this is how being
in love really feels like.
It's like the world is
filled with happiness.
Carmelita.
I will explain.
- Leandro...
- Let me explain it to you.
Stop it!
That's enough!
No matter what you say,
we will never be together!
What happened to you?
Carmelita, why did you completely change?
Why does it seem like
you’re not the Carmelita I knew?
Huh?
No matter what I do
and even if I risk my life for you...
Why can't you recognize my love?
Until now,
you still can't forgive that time I left?
Is that it?!
I left to fulfill my dream.
For the both of us.
It was for the both of us!
You are mistaken, Leandro!
Even though you got
the position you wanted...
Even though you achieved all your dreams...
You and me can never
return to what we were.
Because everything has changed.
Everything has changed?
Or is it because the one
in your heart has changed?
Tell me the truth.
I said, tell me the truth!
Damn it!
Leandro!
What is my worth to you, Carmelita?
Or am I just a shadow from your past?
I loved you with all my honor.
And then...
This is how you treat me?!
You made me a fool out of me.
You played me.
Made me look stupid.
You played me like a fool!
Maybe you thought...
You could wrap me
around your fingers forever.
Right?
General Seleno told me everything.
Even though your father paid him
to shut his mouth.
That means
even before the wedding,
Leandro knew about Juanito and I?
So that's why he helped me
talk to Mother Olivia in prison.
He just wants to make me
fall in back in love with him.
Leandro!
Stop it!
I won't let you and Juanito be happy.
I was the first one you loved.
And I will make sure I'm the one you marry.
Because you belong to me, Carmelita.
You are mine!
Enough!
That person is just around here.
They're always watching you
and everything you do.
What if...
It was Leandro who killed Juanito?
I am not afraid of Leandro.
And I will fight for you until the end.
Don't you believe me?
Don't fret.
Juanito, I believe in you.
The thing is...
Don't ever lose this ever again.
Juanito?
That's just the first bullet.
Leandro!
So that you can't escape.
So that you can't escape.Juanito?
Juanito, don't leave me here.
Don't die.
Leandro, don't!
Did you know that...
You're the one who put Juanito in danger?
So don't you dare blame me
For what I'm gonna do to him tonight.
Leandro...
Don't!
[speaks in Spanish]
Leandro... don't!
Juanito...
Juanito!
Wait, wait! Leandro!
Leandro...
Leandro, I'm begging you!
Just this once, please.
Leandro, don't.
Just this once, Leandro.
Have mercy!
I'm begging you!
Look at me, Leandro.
Leandro, look at me!
You're not a murderer, okay?
Just this once.
Do you remember?
When I asked you
to listen to me explain?
Did you listen?
Leandro...
Leandro, don't.
Watch.
Leandro!
- Wait, no!
- Shoot him.
Wait!
Juanito!
- Leandro!
- Shoot him!
Shoot him!
Leandro!
Damn it!
No!
Leandro, don't!
- Juanito!
- Damn it!
No!
- No... don't!
- You son of a bitch!
No!
Juanito!
Remember, Carmela.
The moment this diary burns by itself,
that is the sign you failed your mission.
That is the sign
that Juanito is dead
I failed my mission.
I failed to stop the death of my beloved.
Miss Carmelita?
Who are you?
I am Belinda,
your new servant.
Esmeralda has been banished
so she couldn't serve you anymore.
Esmeralda was banished
because she covered up for Juanito and I.
From this moment on,
I have no one on my side.
I am truly alone.
Miss Carmelita?
May I let your guest enter?
Alright.
Why are you sulking here?
We've been waiting for three
days for you to come begging.
I will never beg for your mercy.
Well, then.
It seems like Leandro couldn't do anything
to save you and your family.
Not for long,
the rebels will find out that
Juanito died because of you.
Imagine what the jury would think
once they discover that a daughter
of a prominent government official
was in a relationship with a rebel.
Expect that your father
wouldn't be able to do anything
to save you and your
family from their judgment.
That's no problem.
But you and Leandro will
pay for Juanito's murder.
Juanito was a rebel, Carmelita.
And it's Leandro's job
to fight the enemies of the government.
What I just can't accept,
is that even though my
brother Leandro is hurting now,
you're still on his mind.
I don't understand what's
so special about you.
Why does this woman hate me so much?
Maria!
That is beautiful!
The winner is Miss Carmelita Montecarlos.
Now it's clear to me why
Natasha hates us so intensely.
What she went through wasn't so easy.
I don't want Leandro to suffer forever.
That's why I'll help you
and your family survive.
On one condition.
Marry Leandro.
But I will make sure that
your life will be a living hell.
Do you really love your brother?
Or do you just want to make yourself
feel superior than the rest of us?
Who are you to talk to me that way?
You know, you shouldn't
have let envy rule your heart.
If you know you're smart, kind,
and beautiful.
You don't have to compete with all of us.
The moment you
compared yourself to others...
You already lost.
Carmelita?
Helena?
I'm sorry, Carmelita.
I stayed silent and went away.
To get away from my family's cruelty.
Don't feel bad.
Your family's sins are not yours.
You don't understand.
I have long known that
Juanito was falling for you.
Do you remember that time
before Juanito left for Manila?
I went to your house then
and told you I'll accept his proposal.
I was wearing his grandmother's necklace.
But the truth was...
If Sonya didn't ask about that necklace...
Juanito wouldn't give it to me as a gift.
Maybe he was just pressured to do it.
And I am aware that
Juanito really wanted to
give this necklace to you.
But I still forced
myself to believe that...
Juanito was just worried
for you as a friend.
That's why when I learned
that my father had executed
Trinidad's whole family...
I ran away to tell you everything.
But I was deeply hurt
when I saw you and Juanito together.
He gave you an envelope...
I read what's written in it.
And then, I learned that it's you he loved.
That's why I agreed to
Father and Natasha's plan.
To ruin your whole family.
But why?
Because the Alfonso and Montecarlos
families would be too powerful
once you and Juanito get married.
They promised me that I can marry Juanito.
So I waited for him
at the thanksgiving celebration.
There, he confessed.
That you
are the one in his heart.
And then, we were caught by your parents.
When you said that
you still love Leandro...
Father decided to sacrifice
Don Mariano and General Sergio.
They wanted to include Juanito.
But I begged them not to.
In exchange,
I promised to go to Spain.
Forgive me, Carmelita.
I didn't know your sister
and mother would be killed.
I just arrived yesterday.
And I learned that Leandro killed Juanito.
Forgive me, Carmelita.
I'm sorry...
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry, Carmelita.
Now I know that Carmela won't be born.
There won't be a Carmela
to be the first-born daughter
of Mommy Carmenia and Dad.
There won't be a Carmela to be the
eldest sister of Jenny and Emily.
I'm stuck here now,
because I failed my mission.
I will forever be Carmelita Montecarlos.
But I'm hoping
that one day,
my true family will learn
what happened to me.
I'm hoping,
that through this letter,
they will come to understand
why I have decided to end it all.
Perhaps this is where all the
joy, sadness, anger, regret, sorrow,
and love I've felt finally come to an end.
I leave it all here at the Lake of Tears.
Your mission is not over Carmela.
You need to return.
To save the one you love.
Just rest, child.
I'm here to watch over you.
Don't leave us.
Even though he committed
a lot of bad things...
I still cannot blame him.
I was the reason why
he did all those things
that weren't supposed to happen
in Carmela and Juanito's original timeline.
But because I arrived here...
Everything changed.
Is there still a chance for me to go home?
Or am I destined to stay
in this timeline forever?
Maria.
Maria!
My sister...
Maria?
She's gone...
Mother is gone.
She's already gone.
Maria...
Carmelita...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not being here.
For not being by your side.
I heard everything from Eduardo.
Even what happened to Juanito.
I know it hurts a lot.
And I know it feels like
you don't want to live.
But I thank the Lord...
That you're still here with us.
I'm sorry, Maria.
I'm sorry...
It's a good thing
I searched for you immediately.
And when I couldn't find you...
I saw Juanito's necklace in your room.
That you've always worn.
That's when I realized
that you might have done
something to harm yourself.
Belinda and I saw your
slippers at the Lake of Tears.
I waded through the lake immediately.
And that's when I finally saw you...
Slowly sinking into the water.
I thought I was going to lose you as well.
I'm sorry.
I cannot take it anymore.
I give up.
I don't want this.
I understand, Carmelita.
We remember everything.
We must continue with our lives.
For the people who love us.
Mother is gone.
As well as Josefina.
And I will not survive
if you left me as well.
Father Orlando heard about what happened.
And he wants to talk to you.
I suspect the news leaked
because of the servants.
I don't want to, Maria.
Just tell him that I'm already repentant.
Carmelita...
You must be brave.
You must face your problems head-on.
Because nothing will
happen if you just continue
to run away.
Don't worry, child.
The Lord knows that you are
deeply regretting what you did.
Stop your tears, child.
There's something I'd like to show you.
This is me.
Who painted this?
Juanito...
I fulfilled my promise.
That no matter what happens...
I will stay alive.
Bergilio followed me.
When they saw what Leandro did to me,
they informed Catapang right away.
They ambushed Leandro
while they were attempting to dump my body.
They took me to Father Orlando
and begged him to hide me.
I'm happy you already saw this.
Juanito didn't paint Carmelita's portrait.
But why did Juanito paint my portrait now?
I promise...
We'll see each other again in 10 days.
I've been avoiding him for weeks now,
but he still won't give up.
If he discovers that Juanito's still alive,
Leandro might try to kill him again.
Leandro?
Good morning, Carmelita.
This is for you.
How are you?
I had heard
what happened to you at the lake.
Carmelita, you need to learn how to swim.
So that you can save yourself
if you somehow get into the deep.
I visit you everyday
to make sure you're fine.
If...
You wish to bathe in the lake,
I will accompany you.
So that I can ensure your safety.
Don Alejandro didn't tell him
the truth about my drowning.
Did you receive my letter?
The one I handed to Natasha
to give to you?
I hope you'll read it.
You must do something about him, Carmela!
How are you?
I'm good.
Busy at work.
But...
It won't stop me from visiting you.
Maybe if he didn't try to kill Juanito,
we could still be friends.
I did become quite
comfortable in his company.
I long for your kiss.
Why are you...
Pouting your lips?
Are you feeling alright?
Shit, that was just my imagination?
It's just...
Do you feel feverish?
No, I'm just
thankful to you.
That...
You don't take advantage of my weakness.
I have a lot of respect for you, Carmelita.
I am willing to wait no matter how long.
And also,
I'm the only one who's been talking.
It's your turn.
Tell me a story from your childhood.
Hmmm...
My sister and I used to fight all the time
over simple things.
And then
Dad would reprimand us -
I mean, Father.
And then,
he will ground us...
It means he'll lock us in our room.
Carmelita...
I hope we had met when were still young.
I'm sure I will keep so much memories...
About you, forever.
I grew up in Manila.
Because I focused on my studies.
I only came home during
Christmas and the Feast.
Here in San Alfonso.
That's why I don't
know a lot of ladies here.
So that means you got to
know a lot of ladies in Manila?
Yes.
But...
I never fell,
nor courted anyone.
How about Helena?
As for Helena...
During the Thanksgiving to the patron...
Sonya was supposed to introduce me to her.
But she ran away.
That's why when I returned to Manila,
I received a letter from her.
I was only able to reply
maybe once or twice.
To her letter.
That's why when I came home to San Alfonso,
I wanted to meet her.
And right there...
We were caught by Don
Alejandro and my father together.
That means,
when I saw Juanito looking
at Helena's bedroom window,
they still hadn't met one another?
I'll admit.
I was glad
when you helped me
and Helena became closer.
But I cannot get you out of my mind.
I am happier when I'm with you.
My heart gets lighter
when I make you smile.
It didn't take long
for me to realize
I was falling for you.
I learned that you and
Leandro were lovers before.
And I realized then...
That you still love him.
Because you told me
that your first love
went somewhere far away.
I was talking about James Gilbert!
But ...
what makes me happier
is the fact that in the
end, you still chose me.
And I believe
that no matter what happens,
until the end,
you will always choose me.
Carmelita,
please stop!
Juanito, I'm begging you.
Please, I beg you...
Even though Helena is the one you love.
Just marry me.
Because I'm so in love with you, Juanito.
I love you very much.
I'm sorry.
I believe you will find
someone else who will love you.
What are you saying?!
Huh!?
I cannot accept this!
You will regret this...
I swear you will regret all of this!
A payment of gold.
Kill Juanito.
But what if I get discovered...
Captain Flores and Natasha already know.
It's something between the four of us.
I know you desire the position and power
of the Alfonso family.
And the only thing I want...
is the life of Juanito.
Kill him at the end of February.
Miss?
Are you alright?
Did you have a nightmare?
Wait,
Belinda,
why is my room a mess?
Miss...
You were the one who
hung all of these curtains.
You also asked me to buy
you embroidery supplies
and you did nothing but that the whole day.
Belinda, what is the date today?
It's the 2nd day of February, Miss.
That means,
I was out of it for three days.
What happened?
Why can't I remember anything?
I am here.
Oh, Lord...
It was Carmelita who was
behind Juanito's murder.
How can I do my mission if
Carmelita can control my body?
How can you be sure, Juanito?
She has proven time and again,
that she does not agree
with her Father's wrongdoings.
She has also
covered for us several times.
He's at the church in San Alfonso.
He is hidden by Father Orlando.
Why did you
write a letter to Mr. Caloy?
Father is forcing them to confess
which of them is allied with Catapang.
Most of them
have an X mark on their body.
How do you know that?
Which one?
Wait!
Don't come any closer!
Don't!